Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Unterstützen Sie den Administrator! Schauen Sie auf kissasia.cam oder kisskh.org vorbei.
I just feel that with my background
Ich habe einfach das Gefühl, dass mit meinem Hintergrund
it's better not to get too close to you.
Es ist besser, dir nicht zu nahe zu kommen.
What do you mean by that?
Was meinst du damit?
My family are military officers.
Meine Familie besteht aus Offizieren.
We can't afford any trouble.
Wir können uns keinen Ärger leisten.
Civil officials hold power now.
Die Macht liegt nun bei zivilen Beamten.
They've always looked down on us.
Sie haben immer auf uns herabgesehen.
Those of us from military families.
Wir stammen aus Militärfamilien.
And now,
Und nun,
we're just pawns in their factional strife.
Wir sind nur Spielfiguren in ihrem Fraktionskampf.
My father's imprisonment is proof enough.
Die Inhaftierung meines Vaters ist Beweis genug.
I won't let that happen again.
Ich werde das nicht noch einmal zulassen.
The Spring Imperial Examination is over.
Die Frühjahrsprüfung des Kaiserlichen Instituts ist beendet.
The new officials all seek civil-military integration.
Die neuen Amtsträger streben allesamt eine zivil-militärische Integration an.
Soon,
Bald,
that's your concern.
Das ist Ihr Problem.
I just want a peaceful life with my father.
Ich wünsche mir einfach nur ein friedliches Leben mit meinem Vater.
By the way,
Übrigens,
where have you been lately?
Wo warst du in letzter Zeit?
Rui Wang said
Rui Wang sagte
you chased the human traffickers' remnants
Sie jagten die Überreste der Menschenhändler.
and then disappeared.
und verschwand dann.
I chased those remnants
Ich verfolgte diese Überreste.
out of the city.
außerhalb der Stadt.
I didn't expect they had accomplices.
Ich hatte nicht erwartet, dass sie Komplizen hatten.
I was badly injured.
Ich wurde schwer verletzt.
I escaped to the mountain.
Ich bin in die Berge geflohen.
My senior sister saved me.
Meine ältere Schwester hat mich gerettet.
Martial Uncle was worried
Kampfonkel war besorgt
someone in the capital might harm me.
Jemand in der Hauptstadt könnte mir schaden.
So he told me not to leave the mountain until I healed.
Deshalb sagte er mir, ich solle den Berg nicht verlassen, bis ich wieder gesund sei.
He wouldn't let me send any messages either.
Er erlaubte mir auch nicht, Nachrichten zu senden.
So that's what happened.
Das ist also passiert.
Martial Uncle Yu's concern
Die Besorgnis von Kampfonkel Yu
is not without reason.
ist nicht ohne Grund.
Martial Uncle really did a lot for me.
Martial Uncle hat wirklich viel für mich getan.
Nan Chenxiao,
Nan Chenxiao,
let's
Lass uns
move forward.
vorwärts.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
Let's move forward together.
Lasst uns gemeinsam voranschreiten.
Your Majesty,
Eure Majestät,
Miss Qiao.
Fräulein Qiao.
Your Majesty.
Eure Majestät.
Slow down.
Verlangsamen.
Thank you.
Danke schön.
Why did you come up the mountain?
Warum bist du auf den Berg gekommen?
Your Majesty,
Eure Majestät,
I had something to discuss with you.
Ich hatte etwas mit Ihnen zu besprechen.
So I asked Second Young Master Rui to bring us up.
Deshalb bat ich den zweiten jungen Meister Rui, uns heraufzubringen.
But
Aber
we somehow got separated just now.
Wir haben uns eben irgendwie getrennt.
Princess and Second Young Master Rui are missing.
Prinzessin und zweiter junger Meister Rui werden vermisst.
Yan Luo also came up the mountain.
Auch Yan Luo kam den Berg hinauf.
It's all my fault.
Es ist alles meine Schuld.
I wanted to speak with Your Majesty,
Ich wollte mit Eurer Majestät sprechen.
so Second Young Master Rui led us up.
So führte uns der zweite junge Meister Rui nach oben.
Take her back.
Bring sie zurück.
I'll go look for them.
Ich werde nach ihnen suchen gehen.
How long ago did you split up?
Wie lange ist es her, dass ihr euch getrennt habt?
About half an hour ago.
Vor etwa einer halben Stunde.
I came from that direction.
Ich kam aus dieser Richtung.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
Your Majesty,
Eure Majestät,
this is a signal flare.
Dies ist eine Leuchtrakete.
Set it off later,
Verschiebe es auf später,
and the Chongming Guard will come for you.
Und die Chongming-Wache wird dich holen.
Your Majesty,
Eure Majestät,
the Princess got lost because of me.
Die Prinzessin hat sich wegen mir verirrt.
I can't just leave her.
Ich kann sie nicht einfach verlassen.
Please take me with you.
Bitte nimm mich mit.
I won't cause any trouble.
Ich werde keinen Ärger machen.
Then keep up on your own.
Dann bleibe selbstständig auf dem Laufenden.
It's pouring so hard.
Es regnet in Strömen.
Why aren't they back yet?
Warum sind sie noch nicht zurück?
Yeah.
Ja.
Liang Jin.
Liang Jin.
You're back.
Du bist zurück.
You all came back.
Ihr seid alle zurückgekommen.
It's yours.
Es gehört dir.
Thank you, Fu Lu.
Danke, Fu Lu.
Thank you, Lord Chongming.
Danke, Lord Chongming.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Go.
Gehen.
Hold it tight.
Halt es fest.
What are you doing?
Was machst du?
Bring the basin over.
Bring das Becken herüber.
Coming, coming.
Kommt, kommt.
I never thought country life was so fun.
Ich hätte nie gedacht, dass das Landleben so viel Spaß machen kann.
If you like it,
Wenn es Ihnen gefällt,
we can come up the mountain often.
Wir können oft auf den Berg kommen.
Martial Uncle may be a grumpy old man,
Martial Uncle mag ein griesgrämiger alter Mann sein.
but he does enjoy lively company.
Er genießt aber lebhafte Gesellschaft.
Your Majesty and the others won't get lost, right?
Eure Majestät und die anderen werden sich nicht verirren, oder?
Don't worry.
Mach dir keine Sorge.
Youyi grew up on this mountain.
Youyi wuchs auf diesem Berg auf.
She could find her way back with her eyes closed.
Sie könnte den Weg zurückfinden, selbst mit geschlossenen Augen.
Is it that heavy?
Ist es so schwer?
Hold it steady, hold it steady.
Ruhig halten, ruhig halten.
Miss Qiao.
Fräulein Qiao.
Careful.
Vorsichtig.
Watch out, the path is slippery.
Vorsicht, der Weg ist rutschig.
We can take shelter ahead.
Wir können uns schon mal in Sicherheit bringen.
Put it on.
Zieh es an.
Thank you, Miss Qiao.
Vielen Dank, Frau Qiao.
Your Majesty, you should wear it.
Eure Majestät, Ihr solltet es tragen.
No need.
Keine Notwendigkeit.
I see you've been shivering.
Ich sehe, du hast gefroren.
You should wear it.
Du solltest es tragen.
Your Majesty's health is precious.
Eure Majestät, eure Gesundheit ist kostbar.
Your Majesty should wear it.
Eure Majestät sollte es tragen.
You should wear it.
Du solltest es tragen.
Still, Your—
Dennoch, Ihr—
They're just two worthless things.
Es sind einfach zwei wertlose Dinge.
If you both don't want to wear them, forget it.
Wenn ihr beide sie nicht tragen wollt, dann vergesst es.
No need to keep passing them around.
Es ist nicht nötig, sie immer wieder weiterzureichen.
Your Majesty,
Eure Majestät,
your clothes are soaked.
Ihre Kleidung ist durchnässt.
Go dry them by the fire.
Geh und trockne sie am Feuer.
No need.
Keine Notwendigkeit.
If you catch a chill,
Wenn Sie sich erkälten,
who will lead us out?
Wer wird uns herausführen?
That's true.
Das stimmt.
If you two get sick,
Falls ihr beide krank werdet,
I'll be in trouble.
Ich werde Ärger bekommen.
That's not what I meant.
Das meinte ich nicht.
Martial Uncle only has three rooms here.
Martial Uncle hat hier nur drei Zimmer.
We must leave one for Your Majesty.
Wir müssen einen für Eure Majestät zurücklassen.
Chongming and I
Chongming und ich
will squeeze into Martial Uncle's room.
wird sich in Onkel Martials Zimmer quetschen.
You and Youyi will have to share a room.
Du und Youyi müsst euch ein Zimmer teilen.
Miss Qiao, she—
Fräulein Qiao, sie—
She knows everything now.
Sie weiß jetzt alles.
This is clothing from Wurong Kingdom.
Dies ist Kleidung aus dem Königreich Wurong.
Why is there a tear?
Warum ist da ein Riss?
And bloodstains?
Und Blutflecken?
This belongs to Martial Uncle.
Dies gehört dem Kampfonkel.
Maybe when he went to Wurong before,
Vielleicht als er zuvor in Wurong war,
he wore it to gather intelligence.
Er trug es, um Informationen zu sammeln.
I see.
Ich verstehe.
On the mountain,
Auf dem Berg,
the thunder sounds even closer.
Der Donner klingt noch näher.
I used to not be afraid.
Früher hatte ich keine Angst.
From now on, you won't need to be.
Von nun an ist das nicht mehr nötig.
I'm here with you.
Ich bin bei dir.
Nothing can hurt you now.
Dir kann jetzt nichts mehr etwas anhaben.
Young Master Nan
Junger Meister Nan
What is it?
Was ist das?
Your Majesty and the others haven't returned yet.
Eure Majestät und die anderen sind noch nicht zurückgekehrt.
What should we do?
Was sollen wir tun?
Let's go out and look for them.
Lasst uns hinausgehen und sie suchen.
You're awake.
Du bist wach.
The rain has stopped.
Der Regen hat aufgehört.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Wipe yourself off, be careful not to catch a chill.
Wisch dich ab, pass auf, dass du dich nicht erkältest.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Sit closer to the fire too.
Setz dich auch näher ans Feuer.
Don't catch a cold.
Lass dich nicht erkälten.
Weren't we out here to look for my royal brother?
Waren wir nicht hier, um nach meinem königlichen Bruder zu suchen?
How did things end up like this?
Wie konnte es so weit kommen?
Just bear with it for one night.
Halte es einfach eine Nacht lang aus.
Wait until tomorrow.
Warten Sie bis morgen.
Once it stops raining, we can head out.
Sobald es aufhört zu regnen, können wir losgehen.
But I'm hungry.
Aber ich habe Hunger.
This is all we have.
Das ist alles, was wir haben.
Let me see if you have anything else.
Mal sehen, ob Sie sonst noch etwas haben.
Stop searching, it's all medicine.
Hör auf zu suchen, es geht nur um Medizin.
Why bring so many medicine jars and no food?
Warum so viele Medikamentenfläschchen und kein Essen mitbringen?
I'm worried what if we get hurt.
Ich mache mir Sorgen, was ist, wenn wir verletzt werden?
I think the mountain has plenty of resources.
Ich glaube, der Berg verfügt über viele Ressourcen.
Even if we get lost, we can find food.
Selbst wenn wir uns verirren, können wir Essen finden.
But the medicine we need
Aber die Medikamente, die wir brauchen
might not be easy to find right away.
Es könnte etwas dauern, bis man es findet .
Why are you treating me like this?
Warum behandelst du mich so?
Eat one.
Iss eins.
It'll make you feel full.
Davon fühlt man sich satt.
Just one will make you feel full.
Schon eines davon macht satt.
You're really eating it?
Du isst das wirklich?
Feeling full isn't actually being full.
Sich satt zu fühlen bedeutet nicht, tatsächlich satt zu sein.
It's just psychological comfort.
Es geht lediglich um psychologischen Trost.
You...
Du...
What's that sound?
Was ist das für ein Geräusch?
I'm not going to die here, am I?
Ich werde hier doch nicht sterben, oder?
I haven't even met Wang Guanshan yet.
Ich habe Wang Guanshan noch gar nicht getroffen.
I haven't had him write Princess Chunxi's story.
Ich habe ihn noch nicht die Geschichte von Prinzessin Chunxi schreiben lassen.
I'll regret this for the rest of my life.
Das werde ich mein Leben lang bereuen.
This regret—
Dieses Bedauern –
I can help you fulfill half of it.
Ich kann Ihnen bei der Hälfte davon helfen .
You've already met Wang Guanshan.
Sie haben Wang Guanshan bereits kennengelernt.
What are you talking about?
Worüber redest du?
I don't understand.
Ich verstehe nicht.
You, you...
Du, du...
Don't tell me you are—
Sag mir nicht, dass du es bist –
Come.
Kommen.
Your clothes are dry.
Ihre Kleidung ist trocken.
Put them on first.
Zieh sie zuerst an.
Don't catch a cold.
Lass dich nicht erkälten.
What's wrong?
Was ist los?
N-nothing.
N-nichts.
Second Young Master Rui
Zweiter Jungmeister Rui
Second Brother Rui
Zweiter Bruder Rui
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
So polite now.
So höflich jetzt.
Not calling me a bad fox anymore.
Mich nennt ihr nicht mehr einen bösen Fuchs.
I...
ICH...
You first.
Du zuerst.
Don't talk to me yet.
Sprich noch nicht mit mir.
What a pity.
Wie schade.
I was going to tell you
Ich wollte dir sagen
what my next story will be about.
Worum es in meiner nächsten Geschichte gehen wird.
But it seems you're not interested.
Aber anscheinend bist du nicht interessiert.
Then let's go.
Dann los!
What story are you writing?
Welche Geschichte schreibst du?
Tell me!
Sag mir!
What's your next book about?
Worum geht es in Ihrem nächsten Buch?
You didn't finish the carriage story last time.
Du hast die Geschichte mit der Kutsche letztes Mal nicht zu Ende erzählt .
Tell it, tell it!
Erzähl es weiter, erzähl es weiter!
Where did I leave off last time?
Wo hatte ich letztes Mal aufgehört?
There was a princess.
Es gab eine Prinzessin.
She fell for a young master disguised as a man.
Sie verliebte sich in einen jungen Mann, der als Mann verkleidet war.
But this young master disguised as a man
Aber dieser junge Herr, der sich als Mann verkleidet hatte
later married a general's daughter disguised as a woman.
Später heiratete sie die als Frau verkleidete Tochter eines Generals .
What kind of story is this?
Was ist das für eine Geschichte?
Isn't this Nan Chenxiao?
Ist das nicht Nan Chenxiao?
Just missing Brother Yu.
Wir vermissen nur noch Bruder Yu.
He's also disguised as a man.
Er ist außerdem als Mann verkleidet.
Brother Yu isn't the one you're talking about, is he?
Du meinst doch nicht Bruder Yu , oder?
Uh...
Äh...
Miss Qiao
Fräulein Qiao
Qiao...
Qiao...
Who is Miss Qiao?
Wer ist Fräulein Qiao?
Royal brother!
Königlicher Bruder!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Seid gegrüßt, Eure Majestät.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Ich dachte, ich würde dich nie wiedersehen.
Stand up straight.
Stehen Sie gerade.
A princess should behave with dignity.
Eine Prinzessin sollte sich würdevoll verhalten.
And also—
Und außerdem –
Why did you sneak out of the palace again?
Warum bist du schon wieder aus dem Palast geschlichen?
It's because the top beam is crooked, so the lower ones are too.
Das liegt daran, dass der obere Balken schief ist, deshalb sind es die unteren auch.
Princess!
Prinzessin!
Wanwan!
Wanwan!
That's great, that's great!
Das ist toll, das ist toll!
I'm glad you're safe.
Ich bin froh, dass du in Sicherheit bist.
If something happened to you, what would I do?
Was würde ich tun , wenn dir etwas zustoßen würde ?
I'm fine, what about you?
Mir geht es gut, und dir?
I'm fine too.
Mir geht es auch gut.
Let's hurry back.
Lasst uns schnell zurückkehren.
Lord Rui and my junior sister must be worried.
Lord Rui und meine jüngere Schwester müssen sich Sorgen machen.
I'm really fine.
Mir geht es wirklich gut.
Miss Qiao is right.
Frau Qiao hat Recht.
We sheltered from the rain and made a fire.
Wir suchten Schutz vor dem Regen und machten ein Feuer.
I was so worried!
Ich war so besorgt!
I wonder if they found shelter from the rain.
Ich frage mich, ob sie Schutz vor dem Regen gefunden haben.
My lord, slow down.
Mein Herr, verlangsamen Sie.
Stay close.
Bleibt in der Nähe.
Don't get separated.
Lasst euch nicht aus den Augen verlieren.
It's a signal from Your Majesty.
Es ist ein Signal von Eurer Majestät.
That way.
So.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Go.
Gehen.
Let's go, Wanwan.
Los geht's, einer nach dem anderen.
What's wrong?
Was ist los?
Your Majesty, I have something to tell you.
Eure Majestät, ich muss Euch etwas mitteilen.
May I speak with you in private?
Darf ich Sie unter vier Augen sprechen?
Do you have something
Hast du etwas?
you can't let us hear?
Können Sie uns das nicht hören lassen?
Wait here for a moment.
Einen Moment bitte hier warten.
Royal brother.
Königlicher Bruder.
Give your royal brother
Gib deinem königlichen Bruder
some space.
etwas Platz.
So many people going to my master—
So viele Menschen gehen zu meinem Meister –
He might not be happy, not to mention—
Er wäre vielleicht nicht glücklich, ganz abgesehen davon –
What about my junior sister's identity?
Und wie steht es mit der Identität meiner jüngeren Schwester?
That's true.
Das stimmt.
I wonder if there's anywhere to stay on the mountain.
Ich frage mich, ob es auf dem Berg irgendwo eine Unterkunft gibt.
Second Young Master Rui and Yan Luo both know.
Sowohl der zweite junge Meister Rui als auch Yan Luo wissen Bescheid.
It's just—
Es ist einfach so –
Miss Ming
Fräulein Ming
Royal brother, where are you going?
Königlicher Bruder, wohin gehst du?
Don't go over there.
Geh nicht dorthin.
Your Majesty!
Eure Majestät!
You all—
Ihr alle –
What's going on?
Was ist los?
Ming Wanwan, Princess Chunxi,
Ming Wanwan, Prinzessin Chunxi
and your second brother are here.
und dein zweiter Bruder sind hier.
Why did they come?
Warum sind sie gekommen?
They're here to find me.
Sie sind hier, um mich zu finden.
Yan Luo and Rui Wang are both fine.
Yan Luo und Rui Wang geht es beiden gut.
Mainly—
Hauptsächlich-
Why are you staring at me?
Warum starrst du mich an?
Yes.
Ja.
Ming Wanwan.
Ming Wanwan.
This is such a hassle.
Das ist echt lästig.
How about you
Und du
go hide in the room for now, don't come out.
Geh und versteck dich jetzt im Zimmer, komm nicht wieder heraus.
Then how long
Und wie lange?
do I have to hide?
Muss ich mich verstecken?
Tomorrow at dawn,
Morgen im Morgengrauen
I'll go down the mountain with them.
Ich werde mit ihnen den Berg hinuntergehen.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
Let's head back then.
Dann lasst uns umkehren.
Your Majesty, take care.
Eure Majestät, passen Sie auf sich auf.
My master likes peace and quiet.
Mein Herr mag Ruhe und Frieden.
Please rest in the courtyard.
Please rest in the courtyard.
Go down the mountain at first light.
Go down the mountain at first light.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Sorry for disturbing you.
But I'm hungry.
But I'm hungry.
I'll make you something to eat.
I'll make you something to eat.
Thank you, Miss Qiao.
Thank you, Miss Qiao.
You're so kind.
You're so kind.
Come.
Come.
Let's sit for a while too.
Let's sit for a while too.
Let me help you.
Let me help you.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
Are you hungry?
Bist du hungrig?
Food will be ready soon.
Food will be ready soon.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I have something to tell you.
I have something to tell you.
Wait a moment.
Einen Moment bitte.
It's about state affairs.
It's about state affairs.
I...
ICH...
I'll be back soon.
I'll be back soon.
If you need anything,
If you need anything,
just ask Chongming.
just ask Chongming.
Your back must be sore.
Your back must be sore.
What's the matter?
What's the matter?
Pingxiang merchants are about to enter the capital.
Pingxiang merchants are about to enter the capital.
Rui family's eldest brother is in charge.
Rui family's eldest brother is in charge.
But he's always been unruly.
But he's always been unruly.
So I'm worried something might go wrong.
So I'm worried something might go wrong.
That's what my father told me.
That's what my father told me.
It's a complicated matter.
It's a complicated matter.
That's why I'm concerned.
That's why I'm concerned.
You should tell Rui Yu about this.
You should tell Rui Yu about this.
Why are you telling me?
Why are you telling me?
Could it be...
Could it be...
I was too hasty and rude.
I was too hasty and rude.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
I understand.
Ich verstehe.
You've worked hard.
You've worked hard.
It's my duty to do this.
It's my duty to do this.
You've been busy all day.
You've been busy all day.
You must be tired.
You must be tired.
Go inside and rest.
Go inside and rest.
I'm not tired.
I'm not tired.
I can still help out.
I can still help out.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Miss Qiao, you're amazing.
Miss Qiao, you're amazing.
Come to the palace and be my teacher.
Come to the palace and be my teacher.
Princess, I appreciate your kindness.
Princess, I appreciate your kindness.
But I'm used to being free.
But I'm used to being free.
Life in the palace is too restrictive.
Life in the palace is too restrictive.
That's true.
That's true.
I think so too.
I think so too.
Life outside the palace is much more fun.
Life outside the palace is much more fun.
Miss Qiao.
Miss Qiao.
Is this enough?
Is this enough?
It's enough.
It's enough.
Before the rain, I saw the flower's core.
Before the rain, I saw the flower's core.
After the rain, no flower beneath the leaves.
After the rain, no flower beneath the leaves.
Is there something on my face?
Is there something on my face?
That's odd.
That's odd.
Why didn't I notice before?
Why didn't I notice before?
Notice what?
Notice what?
It's nothing.
Schon gut.
When are we having dinner?
When are we having dinner?
Eating in the mountains,
Eating in the mountains,
we have to work first.
we have to work first.
Come.
Come.
Let's shell beans.
Let's shell beans.
But I don't know how.
But I don't know how.
Come, I'll teach you.
Come, I'll teach you.
Let me help you serve.
Let me help you serve.
Wanwan.
Wanwan.
Come help shell beans.
Come help shell beans.
No beans, no dinner tonight.
No beans, no dinner tonight.
Let's do it together.
Let's do it together.
It's so lively.
It's so lively.
What a pity.
What a pity.
We can only stay inside.
We can only stay inside.
Someday,
Eines Tages,
you'll meet them openly and proudly.
you'll meet them openly and proudly.
Take off your coat.
Take off your coat.
I'll help you apply medicine.
I'll help you apply medicine.
Uh...
Uh...
Isn't this a bit inappropriate?
Isn't this a bit inappropriate?
We're husband and wife.
We're husband and wife.
What's wrong with that?
What's wrong with that?
Hurry up.
Hurry up.
Does it hurt?
Does it hurt?
No.
NEIN.
My wound is almost healed.
My wound is almost healed.
No need for more medicine.
No need for more medicine.
Your ears are so red.
Your ears are so red.
Did you catch a cold?
Did you catch a cold?
Stop messing around.
Stop messing around.
I'm not messing around.
I'm not messing around.
Let's sleep.
Let's sleep.
Don't catch a chill.
Don't catch a chill.
There are many poisonous insects here.
There are many poisonous insects here.
Don't get hurt.
Don't get hurt.
I know you're mad at me.
I know you're mad at me.
I came up here to explain things to you.
I came up here to explain things to you.
I'm not angry.
I'm not angry.
Then look at me.
Then look at me.
I just think
I just think
Ming Wanwan
Ming Wanwan
is the one best suited to stand by your side.
is the one best suited to stand by your side.
She's not.
She's not.
She's the most famous talent in the capital.
She's the most famous talent in the capital.
Stunningly beautiful.
Stunningly beautiful.
Graceful and well-mannered.
Graceful and well-mannered.
The Empress Dowager
Die Kaiserinwitwe
likes her very much too.
likes her very much too.
But I don't like her.
But I don't like her.
I like you.
I like you.
You're a cloud in the sky.
You're a cloud in the sky.
I can only chase you from the ground.
I can only chase you from the ground.
Even if our hearts connect, so what?
Even if our hearts connect, so what?
You're not Young Master Lin.
You're not Young Master Lin.
And I'm just Miss Qiao.
And I'm just Miss Qiao.
If military officers regain power,
If military officers regain power,
our statuses
our statuses
won't be an unbridgeable gap.
wird keine unüberbrückbare Kluft sein.
Tonight, the mountain wind feels warmer.
Heute Abend fühlt sich der Bergwind wärmer an.
Yes.
Ja.
Spring is here.
Der Frühling ist da.
It's getting warmer.
Es wird wärmer.
You're awake.
Du bist wach.
Sleep a bit more.
Schlaf noch ein bisschen.
Why are you up already?
Warum bist du schon wach?
What if Miss Ming and the others see you?
Was, wenn Miss Ming und die anderen dich sehen?
Youyi already took them down the mountain.
Youyi hat sie bereits vom Berg heruntergebracht.
They've gone down.
Sie sind untergegangen.
Everything that needed to be said is said.
Alles, was gesagt werden musste, ist gesagt.
Staying here is pointless.
Hier zu bleiben ist sinnlos.
The mountain air is so fresh.
Die Bergluft ist so frisch.
I want to come back and visit again.
Ich möchte wiederkommen und Sie erneut besuchen.
Next time,
Nächstes Mal,
I'll take you to climb another mountain.
Ich nehme dich mit auf eine andere Bergbesteigung.
Sure!
Sicher!
Careful!
Vorsichtig!
It's fine.
Das ist in Ordnung.
Princess, slow down.
Prinzessin, langsamer.
Watch out.
Achtung.
You're being too careless.
Du bist zu unvorsichtig.
Wanwan, slow down.
Wanwan, mach langsamer.
Be careful.
Seien Sie vorsichtig.
Just keep walking straight on this path
Folgen Sie diesem Weg einfach immer geradeaus.
and you'll reach the foot of the mountain.
und du erreichst den Fuß des Berges.
Miss Qiao, aren't you coming with us?
Fräulein Qiao, kommen Sie nicht mit uns?
No.
NEIN.
I'm staying on the mountain a while longer.
Ich bleibe noch eine Weile länger auf dem Berg.
Let's part ways here, then.
Dann trennen sich unsere Wege hier.
Alright.
In Ordnung.
Goodbye, Miss Qiao.
Auf Wiedersehen, Fräulein Qiao.
Farewell.
Lebewohl.
Let's go.
Lass uns gehen.
Take it slow.
Lass es langsam angehen.